# CONTACT INFORMATION

404-556-3984

2350 8th Ave S. Apt #422, Nashville, TN 37204

cncowart@gmail.com

https://github.com/cncowart

in www.linkedin.com/in/corycowart

## SKILLS SUMMARY

SOL

Python

Tableau

PowerBI

Excel

Zoom

Slack

#### **PROJECTS**

Lahman Baseball https://github.com/cncowart/lahm an-baseball-SQL

 SQL Analysis of large baseball dataset over the years, answering multiple in depth questions

App Trader https://github.com/cncowart/apptrader-SOL

 Team project that used SQL analysis of App Store datasets to then pitch the most valuable apps

# **CORY COWART**

## JUNIOR DATA ANALYST

#### OBJECTIVE

Junior Data Analyst seeking new challenges and a career transition to an analytical position utilizing SQL, Python and other analysis tools.

## DATA ANALYTICS

# Junior Data Analyst

Nashville Software School | Sept. 2020 - Jan 2021

4 month intensive Data Analytics program covering Excel, SQL, Tableau, PowerBI and Python. The program features real world data and experience in both a team and an individual setting.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Tech

MPower - Elite Sports Medicine and Orthopedics | Aug 2018 - Sept 2020

Sports physical therapy clinic providing treatment to athletes and active adults recovering from various surgeries

- Assisted therapists in treatment of over 250 clients in a sports training and physical therapy atmosphere
- Effectively used knowledge of therapy exercises and relationship building to help in the recovery process of clients

## Senior Tech

Reid Clinic Sports Therapy and Spine | June 2015 - June 2018

Therapy clinic providing physical therapy for patients of all ages

- Successfully tracked inventory needs of the clinic
- Assisted clients in new client check-in and scheduling including providing paperwork and taking insurance information
- Effectively maintained strong, professional relationships with clients to ensure their comfort and success in physical therapy
- Facilitated the sale of therapy equipment to clients
- Assisted head therapist in ongoing treatment of over 300 clients with various injuries and recovery needs, working with each client on a personal basis during their appointment

## **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

Nashville Software School
Data Analytics Cohort | Jan 2020

University of Georgia

B.S. Biology | May 2015